<?xml version="1.0"?>
<book>
	<bookinfo>
		<title>LuaJ Shell</title>
		<author>
			<firstname>Zigmantas</firstname><surname>Kry&#382;ius</surname>
		</author>
	</bookinfo>
	<chapter id="overview"><title>Overview</title>
		<para>
			To use the plugin, first start it, then open up the Console dockable and select the LuaJ shell.
			Once selected, it will attempt to start up the Read-Eval-Print-Loop, and if successful,
			the LuaJ prompt will be displayed. If not successful, the LuaJ plugin
			may need to be configured. Refer to that plugin's documentation for information
			on how to configure it.
		</para>
		<para>
			If you want to have an external library available inside the shell, simply add it to
			the classpath in Plugins -> Plugin Options -> Classpath, then restart the shell
			if necessary.
		</para>
	</chapter>
	<chapter id="actions"><title>Evaluating Code</title>
		<para>
			The easiest way to evaluate code in the shell is to simply type it in and hit enter.
			However, this shell works in a more restrictive way than the Lua interpreter REPL.
			There are several actions available that make it easier to test a portion of your
			code without having to manually copy and paste it.
		</para>
		<para>
			These actions can be found in the menu Plugins -> LuaJ Shell. Using these actions, you can
			use the shell to evaluate the active buffer, any selected text within that buffer,
			or an external LuaJ script.
		</para>
		<para>
			Any variables or functions defined in the shell will persist until the loop is
			manually stopped and restarted.
		</para>
	</chapter>
	<chapter id="stop-restart"><title>Stopping and Restarting</title>
		<para>
			To stop the loop, click on the Stop button in the Console dockable. After it's stopped,
			hit Enter to start it back up again. Restarting can be used to reset the environment,
			or you can simply stop the loop to conserve system resources.
		</para>
	</chapter>
	<chapter id="contacts"><title>Contacts</title>
		<para>
		Author's contact: <email id="email">zigmas.kr@gmail.com</email>.
		</para>
	</chapter>
</book>
